<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../style/slides.xsl"?>

<sprintreview folder="121212" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../style/sprint-review.xsd">
    <team name="Shebang">
        <productowner>Marius Swanepoel</productowner>
        <scrummaster>Johan Tré</scrummaster>
        <member>Thomas Martens</member>
        <member>Stefan De Smit</member>
        <member>Plamen Ivanov Valtchev</member>
        <member>Priyanka Sharma</member>
    </team>

    <stories>
        <story title="TIF2TTOM - Move relationship features to the complex table." state="story done" points="3">
            <slides>
                <slide type="story-narrative">
                    <ul>
                        <li>In GDF, relationships and complex features are quite similar.</li>
                        <li>In GDF, maneuvers are being modelled as relationships, while in TTOM, they are being modelled as complex features.</li>
                        <li>This leads to anomalies in the GDF dataloader code.</li>
                        <li>It is not possible to simply translate GDF relations into TTOM associations.</li>
                        <li>Moving the GDF relationship features that are not pure TTOM associations to the GDF complex table, could simplify the GDF dataloader code a lot.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <h5>The following features where moved from relationship to complex.</h5>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Prohibited Maneuver, Priority Maneuver, Implicit Turn, Prohibited U Turn Maneuver, Restricted Maneuver, Calculated Prohibited Maneuver</li>
                        <li>Bifurcation, Signpost Information, Lane Connectivity, Image Maneuver</li>
                        <li>Grade separate crossing</li>
                        <li>Linear Assignment Maneuver</li>
                    </ul>
                </slide>
                <slide type="story-demo">
                    <header>
                        <h4>Validation results: Relation table no longer has complex features</h4>
                    </header>
                    <img src="img/DIFF_RELTYPE" alt="demo: diff" />
                </slide>
                <slide type="story-demo">
                    <header>
                        <h4>validation results: Relation features are modelled as complex</h4>
                    </header>
                    <img src="img/DIFF_FEATCLASS" alt="Validation process" />
                </slide>
            </slides>
        </story>
        <story title="Release haystack-server, check-out enabled." state="story not-done" points="3" percentage-done="50">
            <slides>
                <slide type="story-narrative">
                    <ul>
                        <li>Check-out enabled, means loading data from the Master Data Store</li>
                        <li>Code is adapted but, during validation, issue in both coredb-main-client and haystack-server were found</li>
                        <li>All known issue are tackled but, needs re-validation</li>
                        <li>Release will be made asap.</li>
                    </ul>
                </slide>
            </slides>
        </story>
    </stories>
</sprintreview>
